[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Each student must ____ a Web site based upon his or her major research project.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The study of how computers are ____ to human brains is called artificial intelligence or AI.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Learning lots of academic words will ____ your chances of success in school.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What is the next letter in the ____ O, T, F, S, N, E, _?", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some, but not many, drivers do not ____ to increases in the price of petrol by using their car less frequently.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "ESL students ____ better in classrooms where the teacher is aware of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ student at our school spends about 90 minutes doing homework every evening.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One ____ reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in labour productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Depression can range from sense of tiredness, low motivation and concentration, to ____ difficulties with managing one's daily life.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The main ____ of teaching should be to teach the students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this paper we describe simple identification and signature schemes which enable any user to ____ his identity and the authenticity of his messages.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new government plans to ____ the best possible health service for all of its citizens.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The main ____ of a good teacher is knowledge of his or her subject.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government announced that it was pleased with the ____ fall in unemployment during its term in office.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students must exhibit a working knowledge of a foreign language by translating a mathematical ____ into English.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of ____ like a camera, it helps to have a diagram to look at.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not ____ the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a positive racial identity.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Through the ____ and its constant updating, people will be able to discover new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It quickly became apparent, however, that someone forgot to ____ the president of this decision.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new government has not yet proved itself ____ of making the right decisions in its foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "First, you will need to gather ____ information about all of the supporting questions.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and ____ employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Hypotenuse is a ____ that you will normally hear only in mathematics class.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to ____ information about patterns of ties among social actors.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teachers are not universally in favour of the school's plan to introduce ____ working times.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Lorelei's fine efforts in starting and maintaining the list have done much to ____ group communication and interaction.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is easy to ____ the government for its failures, but no-one has come up with any better ideas.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In all cases, employers must offer ____ dates for a second-round interview if the date originally suggested is inconvenient.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ teaching methodology will not be successful in a class with many different nationalities and abilities.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "No wonder your computer doesn't work. You must ____ it to the monitor!", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "All political parties have websites these days to ____ people of their policies.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There are six categories to ____ from, each containing five answers in ascending order of difficulty.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most older cultures seem to accept volcanoes as a natural part of life and ____ their habits accordingly.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is impossible for the government to ____ the wishes of all its citizens.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Car companies spend a ____ sum of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The merger of two sellers of that product in the area could not ____ market power significantly.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is still somewhat of a risk to ____ things on the internet.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I don't think she realises the ____ of the task she has set herself.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ its success in fighting unemployment.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has succeeded in reducing unemployment ____ older people; conversely, young people are having ever more difficulty finding a job.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ethnographic reports were clear and did not ____ conflicting information.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Latin alphabet did not ____ between the vowel and consonant sounds of i and u.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was a ____ decision, but ultimately I think it was the student life that had the greatest impact on my decision to come to Wheaton.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Ask the candidate to ____ what they believe to have been their most significant challenges and accomplishments in their current job or a previous job.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You can ____ of old batteries in the container outside the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A concise and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too ____ or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Medical scientists have done extensive research on individual drugs but they do not know so much how drugs ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by distance education students and ____ students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Ventures like Amazon.com will only continue to ____ as long as they make money.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She expects to complete her education and ____ her doctorate between 2012 and 2015, after which she intends to become a mathematics professor.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "contemplate", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to ____ information about patterns of ties among social actors.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ to develop a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a ____ to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It isn't the government's fault if people ____ advice to live healthily.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is a ____ example of the government passing a law that everyone was happy with.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they ____ for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Each of these mechanisms has been investigated with a variety of blood sucking insects and the results clearly show that mosquitoes cannot ____ AidS.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Transportation is not an important ____ in the marketing cost of the new product.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I have no intention of being a teacher when I leave school. I want to ____ more money!", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Do you think that the school will ____ the suggestion to increase the number of holidays?", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People who suffer from hay fever cannot have real flowers in their house. They have ____ ones instead.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is still too soon to ____ how important this invention will be.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A common science ____ for young people is to investigate the growth of plants under different soil, light and water conditions.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Successful applicants will have to provide evidence of medical insurance for the ____ of their stay in the Ukraine.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not many people will change their habits or lifestyle ____ because a government minister tells them it's a good idea.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Chromatography is a separation technique that is used in ____ all branches of science and technology.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to ____ problem-solving strategies that offer clear practical solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this paper we describe simple identification and signature schemes which ____ any user to prove his identity and the authenticity of his messages.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The time when Hitler was leader of Germany is possibly the most terrible ____ in all of history.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Poor results in end of year tests often ____ that the teacher has not taught the course very well.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to ____ a photograph when you apply for a job.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you want to comprehend what is happening in Afghanistan, it is ____ to go there yourself.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Tai Chi is a ____ example of an art of self-defense that can be used effectively by both women and men.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Customers found no benefit in ____ -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His written work is actually very good, but he has ____ problems with the difficult English spelling system.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was an extremely conservative institution, and did not ____ its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Assad did not want to ____ a cease-fire until Israel evacuated at least those parts of the Golan Heights occupied in the October war.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you are eligible for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not ____ Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The points that you ____ should be proportional to the individual's contribution to your team for the quarter to date.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She found that the document had no detail and conflicted with the assessments of ____ intelligence.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Could you please ____ to our Christmas collection for flood victims in Bangladesh?", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ of sentimentality in Weil's notion of the beauty and order of the world.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this field of study will have ____ opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To set up a practice test, I'd create a zero point test with questions from the year before in ____ order with ____ answers.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action ____ to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a teacher educator, I believe that new teachers need to ____ on, critically analyze, and evaluate their own teaching.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's a ____ attack on any community's authority to develop and implement housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions suppress the need for communication or being able to freely ____ your emotions?", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The workers participated in an ____ to see if they worked harder with music in the background.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her work has continued to ____ since the divorce of her parents.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Truman managed to win a narrow ____ with 49.5 percent of the popular vote.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the context of competitive sports, and ____ elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a flexible ____ that can respond and adapt to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The price of stamps will increase only if the total volume of mail does not decrease and the postal ____ does not become more efficient.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some, but not many, drivers do not ____ to increases in the price of petrol by using their car less frequently.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is not the correct ____ to use when comparing two separate databases.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is noted that the university regulations stipulate that a ____ can be offered only if a minimum number of students is enrolled.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company directors invited the workers' union to participate in a meeting to ____ the new factory.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ that at least 80% of the students will pass with the top grade.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The many demonstrators on the streets of the capital city were a clear ____ of the government's unpopularity.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this ____ of the survey, having an explicit privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My science teacher returned my homework and told me to do it again. She said I had to use the ____ format for lab reports.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The essay asks students to complete several tasks, giving the students ____ examples of human rights cases.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police have decided not to ____ the identity of the men arrested for planting the bombs.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government gave an ____ of its plans to change taxation. The full report will not be ready until next year.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many buildings ____ during earthquakes and kill the people inside.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This ____ is subject to formal revision before publication in the university journal.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two ____ professionals who must struggle with the death penalty regularly.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The factory worker was awarded \ufffd\ufffd30,000 ____ for losing his arm in an accident.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion ____ the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a teacher educator, I believe that new teachers need to reflect on, critically analyze, and ____ their own teaching.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The computer lab is ____ to the library.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Although there are a number of credible strategies for trying to ____ employees, money appears to be the most powerful retention tool with regard to top performers.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Department Coordinator, elected by peers, has the same one vote as the others and has no ____ over her peers.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The entire structure of Iraqi military and civil society collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a ____ problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although the mountain was not steep, the raging river could not ____ with sufficient rapidity to prevent its overflowing its banks.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results from this experimental course ____ very clearly that flow visualization can be performed successfully by a wide range of people.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Hopes continue to ____ that a peace treaty can be negotiated.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The study of how computers are similar to human brains is called ____ intelligence or AI.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We have a ____ amount of information about the National Forests in North Carolina on this web site.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of effort invested in her language teaching she was not able to ____ grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Developments in computer technology may eventually make ____ weather forecasting possible.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The system uses a ____ inference engine that does not require users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The communication ____ is a computer, phone line, and modem; the student must have access to the necessary equipment.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ from Frankfurt to Oberursel is about 12 kilometers.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the ____ did not acknowledge the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For financial reasons the government had to cut the ____ to help prisoners on their release from jail.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It should be obvious that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the ____ cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his career in ____ to assure his political survival.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government had to ____ from its starting position in the face of massive criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The treatment must not risk ____ to any personal or public property.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are caught drinking and driving, this results in an ____ driving ban of at least 3 months.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Users want to maximize their access to ____ information, without losing sight of the amount of energy it takes them to get that information.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to ____ the vast mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an ____ on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a legitimate issue.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will ____ attempt to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I don't believe you made a ____ effort to improve. Your grades certainly have not got better.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has made ____ arrangements to control the number of demonstrators on the streets.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, despite the ____ high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to ____ or postpone the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Intelligence is just one ____ in being a successful student. You also have to show initiative and perseverance.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The requirements ____ to decrease family and individual student control over the transition process.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The new law will ____ unmarried mothers.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The last week of the tennis tournament will ____ the first week of the Olympic Games.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this article, a ____ way of teaching chemistry is presented that uses contemporary music and chemical lyrics to educate.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government decided to alter its economic ____ after three years of very slow growth.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I ____ that she will not be given a permanent job at the school.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a rapid ____ in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to ____ its duties.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed assent of the student and signed ____ of the parent.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This document contains a ____ of what scientists think happened at Loihi in the summer of 1996, based upon geological, geophysical, geochemical and biological evidence.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The court also held that because of the contract between the classification ____ and the shipyard, the owners operated the ship under the French flag.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary ____ of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There has been no ____ statement about the number of soldiers who were killed in the fighting.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "D. perceives this as deviation from what she considers the traditional ____ of behaviour of Greek women.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government should pay particular attention to reducing unemployment ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We ____ all our efforts and resources to the education and preparation of all students.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An important clue to understanding volcanoes is knowing the ____ of the volcanic bands.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Look at the ____ of your homework planner! You will have to buy a new one.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief ____ for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It has no ____ but to appeal to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to support Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police have decided not to ____ the identity of the men arrested for planting the bombs.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school has installed emergency buttons in each classroom as a ____ against intruders.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are making very rapid ____ in learning English! You only started learning a year ago, and you can already speak quite fluently.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The university intend to make some changes in its admissions policy, but it cannot yet ____ what those changes will be.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teaching ____ is under siege from an increasing number of social, economic and political factors, leading to large, unmanageable classrooms.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ its goal of reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of all your hard work is an excellent score in your final test. Well done!", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government politicians ____ that the proposed tax changes will lift thousands of people out of poverty.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ to make cannabis legal in small amounts is a significant shift in the government's policy.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What is absent in your essay is any reference to the ____ of your ideas.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unlike other animals, humans have no ____ for survival; we often choose to do things that may be detrimental to our health.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For some people the ____ of a car is more important than its price or performance.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an ____ security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The regime, which is bound to ____ under the deadweight of its own internal contradictions, is going to ____ on our heads.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We must ____ the trend of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He also was able to ____ in identifying outstanding science curriculum materials for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If we learn to ____ effectively with others and are willing to risk sharing our own feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The principal made no ____ on the reasons for asking the student to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Picasso's impulse to draw ____ expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of the new hotel has been well-chosen: halfway between the airport and the beach.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government decided to increase its ____ to the countries of eastern Africa.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the price of petrol ____ to rise, many people will not be able to use their car so often.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You have not made a clear enough ____ between the causes and effects of the disaster.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His written work is actually very good, but he has ____ problems with the difficult English spelling system.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first exhaust all possibilities for Federal and state financial aid programs before seeking ____ loans.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Waldorf Education method considers the teacher's own development to be a significant factor in the educational ____ of the children.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a ____ implication on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school has set up a ____ so that less wealthy students can attend.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In most school parents are asked to consent to their child participating in sex ____ lessons.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The price of stamps will increase only if the total ____ of mail does not decrease and the postal service does not become more efficient.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We are heading for a ____ in our health system. Not enough people want to be doctors.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her grades will start to ____ unless she cuts back on the number of after-school activities she does.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The quality of your ideas and organization is much more important than the ____ of words you write.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teachers allege that the school ____ is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is ____ responsible for the disaster of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We need to ____ a new strategy. This one isn't working.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Over the same period research was unable to measure ____ effects on achievement from readily available school characteristics.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When faculty members assign an Incomplete grade they must ____ the work required.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They were small-minded people and could not ____ students who were superior them.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Perhaps we will have to ____ the issue of the 'Child Friendly City'.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a ____ implication on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Job applicants often find that their personal attributes match what a company values; when this occurs, you should ____ these attributes in your CV.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to travel at half-price on the trains and buses in Frankfurt, you need a ____ identity card with the school stamp.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The desire to be recognized, to be considered important is not superficial. It is a ____ human drive.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We designed an experiment to ____ blood from embryonic rats.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A student should ____ a Literature minor by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not ____ between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Court determined, however, that evidence concerning Ms. Lewinsky was not ____ to the core issues in this case.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Since the U.S. flu vaccine supply was cut in half early this month, shots are scarce, lines long and some people are ____ to miss out.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you presume will come from the M31 ____ - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The State Department has seen a drastic ____ in passport applications being filed since a recent change in policy.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The single, vital, ____ on which the true republic must found itself, he insists, is the ____ of good-will.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If the individual knows in ____ when he or she wishes to apply for time away from the workplace, the individual should complete the preliminary request form.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although nuclear power does not pollute the air, many people are ____ it because they fear an accident or terrorist attack on a nuclear power station.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What is your ____ to paying higher taxes in order that more schools and hospitals can be built?", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ student at our school spends about 90 minutes doing homework every evening.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People are right to be suspicious of any diet that promises ____ success.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The combination of natural and human systems adds an additional ____ of complexity to the interactions.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She will always ____ not going on to college right after high school, and learned the hard way that the educated get all the best that life has to offer.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is unclear why the Massachusetts legislature has refused to ____ the Zoning Act.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater ____ that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They met resistance from Nigerian government officials who did not welcome change and did not want to hear the ____ about the AidS epidemic in Nigeria.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ gave the young criminal his final warning. Next time he stole, he would be sent to prison.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student should declare a Literature ____ by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company made a radical reduction in its workforce in order to ____ its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The unexpected ____ of flu vaccine during winter 2004/2005 caused widespread concern.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "At first there was a little ____ between the Japanese and Korean students, but this soon passed.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ is being used to gather information about the current level of frustration with computers and the extent to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The debate over whether North Korea will ____ and whether the United States should promote its ____ has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Distance learning is the most significant ____ occurring in higher education today.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There will be a ____ class after school today for those who want extra practice for the test.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we assume that the ____ of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a ____ way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Rumours about teachers ____ quickly through schools.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He naturally failed to ____ the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When morality comes up against profit, it is ____ profit that loses.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a ____ increase in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The images in this collection are in the ____ domain. You do not need to ask for permission to use them.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "On-line learning applications will continue to multiply as educational institutions and. business corporations seek new ways to ____ their services.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some steps you can take to ____ yourself and your property are: Lock your room when sleeping and when you leave your room.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "More than 70 percent of the surveyed firms said that the lack of housing was not a ____ on their ability to expand.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug ____ underlie many serious health problems.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Children are able to ____ between reality and fantasy between the ages of 3 and 5, according to new research.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Teachers can ____ that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers often ____ student grammar errors with a yellow marker pen.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The University of Maryland team is particularly focused on using their device to test drugs that may ____ cell-to-cell \"quorum-sensing\".", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While I don't present this as ____ the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The committee was tasked to review the tests and criteria used to determine ____ disability for purposes of eligibility for health Insurance benefits.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The final ____ presents the impact of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their effect on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Think about what you want to describe and the ____ impression you want to give your readers.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "After the war, Turing joined the National Physical Laboratory to work on the ____ of a computer.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the consistent use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be ____ the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ consequence of these wars is the social unrest, and the increasing economic and social divergence between the groups of the community.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity ____ topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Military historians and other students of international security, gradually got into the ____ of meeting together to discuss ideas.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Howard has many chances to ____ into a better father and husband, but he fails to do so.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people say that he does not ____ the qualities to become president of this country.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The construction of the Interstate Highway System ran into serious financial problems because Congress did not ____ the cost of inflation.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school has set up a ____ so that less wealthy students can attend.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Upon completion of your program requirements, you will need to apply for a ____ to teach in the state of Ohio.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school had to pay a small ____ to the parents of the boy who hurt his arm on the ski trip.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What did Louis XIV hope to accomplish in his ____ and foreign policies?", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The causes of gun and knife crime among young people is an important ____ of inquiry.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The President accepts full responsibility for the decision to ____ the rescue.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had found a large ____ of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no need to enumerate in ____ the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to ____ the directions of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They must not be allowed to ____ the emergence of a competitive market economy.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Water is a useful and necessary thing, but it is not a ____ until someone builds a fence around the water source.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a convenient way to obtain energy, but it creates a ____ amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to ____ him and inform him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no doubt about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is ____ dead.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "People today have become more conscious of their individual responsibility to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They are planning to ____ a new bridge behind the school.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Furthermore, the system can also measure environmental conditions in the ____ surroundings including ambient light level, humidity, and temperature.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The book had arrived in ____s by Sunday evening but ____ managers were under strict instructions not to even open the boxes and put it on the shelves.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Be ____ to answer the question in its entirety. Be ____ to explain how and why you came to a particular conclusion.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ocean is a ____ of both freedom and escape.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Revenue from ____ tax is expected to be lower this year than in previous years.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but instead thought we should have the ____ to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To launch the project, a special event will ____ at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An international school is a place that cannot survive if there is ____ that certain groups of students are better than others.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The penalty for her ____ absences will be a poor grade in the final exam.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to acknowledge the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "European democratic nation states have increasingly lost ____ over the conduct of their own economies.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The results are not at all satisfactory, and considerable discontent has arisen ____ the Indians on account of the issues that are being made.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The purpose of this study is to investigate the ____ that men are better in mathematics than women.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar ____ of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Try to communicate that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an ____ solution.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's ____ plan was to close down only one of their factories. Because of continuing bad sales, however, they were forced to close three of them.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we ____ just a little more, we will see that random is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After much debate the school has decided to ____ students with physical disabilities.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "That plan specifies that only the top 12.5 percent of California high school graduates should be considered ____ for UC admission.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a ____ consideration in the purchase decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you offend ____ the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Richards understood the importance of her position, the ____ that she projected and the need to preserve her papers and records at the Center.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A popular type of TV ____ shows people who escape the contemporary world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers fear that the problems in the Middle East may strain the ____ between some of the Arab and Israeli students at the school.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Scientists have not been able to ____ that the fossil is in fact that of a dinosaur.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Groups should advise the instructor if a ____ is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We still don't know if this is really the correct mechanism to ____ the imbalance between matter and antimatter that we observe.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We should never praise or ____ any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company was in a very strong ____ after winning a million dollar contract to build its machines.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people believe that ____ prison penalties for young criminals offend natural justice.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was not ____ to many people why the government had decided to ban smoking in all restaurants but to allow it in its own buildings.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project ____ date.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the political ____ needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They ____ decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no place for those who have failed to strive to better themselves with the ____ afforded them.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Can someone please return this science ____ to the store cupboard?", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "China did not ____ nuclear weapons. Having produced several hundred warheads, China stopped building up its military potential.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to ____ the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government's ____ of reducing teenage drinking by raising the price of alcopops has not been very effective.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Tests are ____ when they measure what they claim to measure, and reliable when they measure consistently.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "According to him migrants and refugees do not ____ enough in Dutch society.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I ____ that problems at home are the reason for her poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families ____ the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Why do people still ____ in living near volcanoes?", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The satellite photographs seem to ____ that North Korea is moving much of its army to the border with China.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your answers ____ a lack of care and effort.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an ____ security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You need to be careful not to ____ people that you meet on the internet They may not be who they claim to be..", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In order to claim a project, you must assemble a team of 3 to 6 people within a class and get ____ approval from your professor.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to collaborate ____ our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The bank didn't think that her idea would generate enough money so they refused to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These projects will ____ student learning through the provision of modern technologies.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a teacher educator, I believe that new teachers need to ____ on, critically analyze, and evaluate their own teaching.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Racism and prejudice continue to be a ____ problem in our country.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The text should contain a ____ description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The unexpected ____ of flu vaccine during winter 2004/2005 caused widespread concern.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My parents ____ a lot of money from their investments in internet companies.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All this progress was a ____ of the advance of technology and also of advances in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies ____ that the state was not able to eliminate discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If he was indeed employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his ____ behaviour.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not easy to ____ an abstract idea in picture form so that ESL students can understand it.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During this period she developed her ideas on art, her main one being that the best art did not focus on reality but evoked the ____ of the soul.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ addresses teacher attitudes toward the assignment of homework.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She chose to ____ the hypothesis that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The regime, which is bound to collapse under the deadweight of its ____ internal contradictions, is going to collapse on our heads.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Nowadays nobody attempts to ____ that smoking is bad for the health.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Follow these recommended times for storage in the freezer to enjoy the best quality in flavor and texture and to ____ good nutritive value.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They must not be allowed to ____ the emergence of a competitive market economy.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are ____ much more often, you are in danger of failing the class.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many arguments would not ____ if people would define the words they use.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The more powerful computers will continue to ____ all aspects of life.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My father's contract in Germany will ____ at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors advise that the better way to get and stay healthy is to eat lots of fruit and vegetables and take ____ exercise.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was a very ____ test. Everyone got 100%.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new ____ could lead to widespread use of solar power.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government can ____ its message about the dangers of drinking if it increases the price of alcohol.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will represent a major ____ for society in general.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is an opportunity to ____ a more demanding curriculum while having an equal opportunity to share in the full benefits of university life.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student's answer may not ____ all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or superficial analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief that scaling up HIV ____ counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Each student's experience was so varied that I was unable to ____ common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In order to ____ for the Olympic games 100-meter athletes need to have run under 10.2 seconds at least once this year.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teachers ____ that students will be negatively affected by the construction of a new road just outside many of the classrooms.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Groups should ____ the instructor if a member is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Is the Smartboard just the latest teaching ____ that will be popular for a year or so and then disappear without trace?", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Twins born from the same egg are called ____ twins. They look exactly the same. Fraternal twins look a little different from each other.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Ruhrgebiet is a large ____ area in north west Germany.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "general"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "D. perceives this as deviation from what she considers the traditional ____ of behaviour of Greek women.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to her student teaching commitments Murray was unable to ____ this year's event.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teacher assistant was unable through various interactive ____ to hold class interest, handled questions poorly, and was generally unable to stimulate discussion.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My ESL teacher has the propensity to talk about his ____ school days.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new committee just adds another layer to an already ____ decision -making process.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to ____ patients to stop smoking. The habit is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students are strongly recommended to ____ assistance from the Student Rights Officer at their campus should they decide to appeal against exclusion.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Wurtz said that these products are not just ____ unnecessary, they are even potentially dangerous.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many of the students were unable to ____ the relevance of the mathematics they had learned and so could not make use of it.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His beliefs were not ____ enough to withstand the influence of the people worked with.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It should be ____ that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the prime cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The student was ____ active with the experiment and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no need to enumerate in ____ the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Chromatography is a separation technique that is used in ____ all branches of science and technology.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not really her ____ that she comes late to school so often. She lives a long way away, and often gets stuck in a traffic jam.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers fear that the problems in the Middle East may ____ the relationship between some of the Arab and Israeli students at the school.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and ____ factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ success in school if you are absent so often.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The nine women here say the poor treatment of ____ workers is an apartheid-era relic that has no place in democratic South Africa.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "So maybe people who see media studies as too general, too loose, too intellectually ____ have a point.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax expert to ____ its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company is investigating ____ of increasing its business in Asia and Africa.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I can survive on a ____ income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Therefore, if a calf has not received an adequate amount of quality colostrum, the calf may not be able to ____ disease.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, indeed devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a list of the local doctors who can speak English.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police had difficulty in trying to ____ the enormous crowd after the pop concert.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Latin alphabet did not ____ between the vowel and consonant sounds of i and u.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to enlarge the amount of land ____ for pasture.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police ____ that they are doing all they can to find the missing child.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Odland demonstrated the ability to run a significant ____ with a wide geographical spread.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to illustrate how the ____ works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mild pain and inflammation can often ____ an otherwise rewarding day of skiing.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I am no ____ in animal behavior, but anyone with even a slight knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult novel ____ a reward.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's ____ and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was a ____ noise coming from the classroom above.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Waldorf Education method considers the teacher's own development to be a significant factor in the educational ____ of the children.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Bernstein thinks the ____ is very important to students and that schools should not criticize it.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Do not ____ all your energy in the first 20 minutes. Remember that the game lasts for half an hour!", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "President Tom Gerety announced today that he will ____ on June 30, 2003, after nine years as the head of the college.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Older people should have a ____ check-up at the doctors at least once a year.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The majority of American voters have turned ____ the war in Iraq but not ____ the American troops and not ____ patriotism.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most important ____ of the new design is that it consumes less power.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In recognition of your continuous satisfactory service to the university, you will ____ an award at five-year intervals.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most important feature of the new ____ is that it consumes less power.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This statement does not ____ that the university will be responsible for any other expenses of the above-name student.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Bush's principal ____ for re-election is his war on terrorism, but in fact that's one of the principal reasons he should not be re-elected.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has the ____ of protecting its citizens from terrorist attack, but many people do not agree with the way it is trying to do this.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to ____ him and inform him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the ____ is sure to produce an angry response from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Today we will practise for the ____ test.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He naturally failed to ____ the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with medium grades who ____ help.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You must try to achieve a ____ between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the ____ that urban life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She lied to the ____ and cheated in her test, but because of her family situation, it was decided to allow her to stay.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There was a ____ in the cafeteria at lunch today. The oil for cooking French fries ignited and set fire to the wooden ceiling.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise ____ of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The unit did not cover nuclear weapons in as much ____ as some of my students would have liked.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people are unwilling to address the issue of ____ warming. They claim it is not happening.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "world"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Roman Catholic Church along with the main Protestant denominations in Europe did not ____ the slave trade.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A frequent error in editing is to fix a word or ____ at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to do a better job when you ____ your work. There are far too many unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When you ____ a primary source, you are undertaking the most important job of the historian.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This ____ does not imply that the university will be responsible for any other expenses of the above-name student.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The plants in many of the world's ____ places have not yet been analysed for their possible medical effects.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Please ____ your books and check each other's writing.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His concerts in the U.S. often ____ works by Scandinavian composers; conversely, he introduces American organ works to Scandinavian audiences.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The libraries are in a poor condition and are in ____ need of restocking with new books and journals in both Arabic and English.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dr. Blumenthal begins by analyzing why health care ____ legislation failed to pass Congress in 1994.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you choose to do nothing to ____ to the changing conditions, you will probably make yourself miserable.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We will not ____ unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It started to ____ after much questioning that the reasons for his bad behaviour were problems at home.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main objective of this ESL ____ is to improve students' ability in academic writing.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Scientists have not been able to ____ that the fossil is in fact that of a dinosaur.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When a student comes to a lesson having learned a poor habit, time and money are lost and ____ is postponed.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to exert its ____ to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Before becoming a teacher she worked in the ____ of green technologies.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A thought- provoking ____ suggests we should expect the extinction of intelligent life on Earth soon.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With noise levels of this magnitude, hearing damage is a ____ problem unless some sort of hearing protection is used.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Selecting the panelists is no easy task, and is subject to ____ lobbying.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her poor behaviour, but promised never to repeat it.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice ____ program is barely alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is a direct result of how the black hole deforms space and time, a four-dimensional ____ that Einstein called spacetime.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The basketball team was easily the strongest in the league. They were able to ____ all the other teams.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Seven years is probably long enough to wait for a ____ to a letter before concluding that there will never be one.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most people ____ the airport's plans to finger-print all passengers as an expensive waste of time.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "English may be a global language but it is not yet a ____ tool for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sometimes it becomes more important to modify tried-and-tested methods and habits rather than ____ more resources.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I will not ____ students laughing at the mistakes of other students.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater ____ that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "stage", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Nature was an ____ part of ancient Chinese, Japanese, and Indian literature.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Large numbers of older adult students do not ____ the basic computer knowledge required to attain a job.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the committee failed to specify in sufficient ____ the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have the ____ to change the world, Ballam tells graduates.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has cut its ____ for research into the causes of cancer.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was the result of his ____ that Brazil could afford scientific institutions.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to ____ the person and the institution of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She has made ____ good progress this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They have other business interests to which they ____ their attention, and they may be expected to continue to do so.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The manager used the ____ of the opening of the new factory block to make a speech about future developments.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This page includes materials relating to the continuing ____ over the teaching of evolution and creationism in schools.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When you employ an electrician to do a job in your house, you hope they will be ____ at their job.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no ____ in getting angry with security staff at airports. They have no choice but to follow orders.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Carla Santos, a professor of leisure studies, says our perception of another culture is ____ shaped by accounts of travel writers, who tend to perpetuate cultural stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A primary goal of teaching is conveying ____ knowledge of the subject matter while inculcating curiosity, generating interest, and developing independence.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "China has experienced ____ growth in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We are going to ____ this photograph to poster size and put it on the classroom wall.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The only disappointing part of the book is a portion of the third chapter, which is devoted to an interesting but much too ____ discussion of FDR's foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your ____ task for this lesson is to work together to prepare a presentation on air pollution.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The text should contain a ____ description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He also was able to assist in identifying outstanding science curriculum ____ for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and ____ a diverse global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors advise people to ____ the number of eggs they eat to 2-3 per week.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Biology courses will cover all ____ human or animal body systems.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At this stage of our research we were unable to find a means for accessing the ____ decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your English is ____ improving, but you'll have to make greater effort if you want to get better more quickly.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice reform program is ____ alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She has ____ problems with her spelling. There was hardly a word she got right in the dictation.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As long as the person did not consume large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the ____ on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You have not yet mastered ____ grammar. You still make mistakes like \"he go\" or she don't\".", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When attempting to ____ a food service for an on-campus event, please be sure to ask the following questions.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a genuine example of how the right ____ and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I would be more prepared to ____ with the rules if I understood the reasons for them.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was a loud argument in the cafeteria today. I had to ____ before it turned into a fight.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a precaution ____ influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Through the exhibit and its ____ updating, people will be able to discover new, thought- provoking works of art from around the globe.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we want to maintain support for an open and ____ economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "So if your flower seeds fail to germinate, you, ____ than the seed, are probably at fault.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must comprise achievement that is over and above ____ course activities.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The writer was not careful when taking notes because he does not understand what plagiarism is, or because he is not ____ of what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My ____ does not require contacting people because I intend to use existing or archived material.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Supplementary reading ____ will be mailed to each participant at least two weeks before the broadcast.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A half century ago the conflict over state regulation of railroads was the ____ issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Due to a ____ increase in the number of students the school needs to appoint 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We do not yet know the implication for the government of the ____ rise in house prices.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The main ____ of the committee is to recommend a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was indeed a huge amount for a ____ that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you ____ the stairs by the nurse's office, you will see the cafeteria in front of you.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on ____ matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Immigrants ____ more than 20% of the total population.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His behaviour has not been very ____ since he returned from vacation.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and ____ factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "common"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He said that any art teacher who did not ____ students to ten thousand years of art was \"criminal.\"", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This survey is being used to gather information about the current ____ of frustration with computers and the extent to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Dogs keep dying: Too many owners ____ unaware of toxic dog food.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Her grades are low because of her ____ inability to turn work in on time.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly degenerate if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an ____ minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our primary mission is to help you identify, plan for, and achieve your ____ goals.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher ____ at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He has a ____ chance of getting in to Oxford University if he gets top scores in all his exams.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Forests are both an important part of the ____ ecosystem and an important resource of raw materials for lumber, paper, and fuelwood.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her work has continued to ____ since the divorce of her parents.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Whatever I write on the board in class as the next day's assignment will always ____ what is printed in the Class Schedule below.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "rational", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to reveal the secret until means have been found to ____ the bomb.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Because of their mobile lifestyle, they did not ____ many objects.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In an era of privatisation and market rule we are facing the fact that ____ments will have to ____ a bit more.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students, staff and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the public should be allowed to ____ classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The two parties paid for these mistakes through ____ poor performance in the final national elections.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government must continue to make every effort to ____ young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the background before you ____ the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For many persons these are not ____ concerns but profound and deep beliefs.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All around the school are small white boxes which can ____ smoke and set off the fire alarm.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Just follow the on-screen instructions as you ____ the discussion forum from within a course.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If a student is caught with drugs in the building, the school will ____ him or her.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a ____ for selection.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ me from the trip list. I will not be able to go.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a ____ domestic situation would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can ____ your risk of getting a cold in the winter if you avoid others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of this website is to help ESL students learn English as enjoyably and effectively as possible.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Antarctica is a very ____ environment. Many explorers have lost their lives there.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you accept a housing ____ in the Summer Allocation and subsequently cancel it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to do a better job when you ____ your work. There are far too many unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "List the specific things you did to ____ strong performance in your project.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Can you please ____ this letter to your parents?", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Furthermore, as an educational institution, the College cannot ____ the background and perspectives of its students and must attempt to promote teaching practices and a campus atmosphere that benefits and ensures the success of all of its learners.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What did Louis XIV hope to accomplish in his ____ and foreign policies?", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the ____ between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to ____ how grammar and usage errors can interfere with meaning.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university's plan to admit more students from poor backgrounds is an exercise that is not ____ to succeed.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with ____ grades who deserve help.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is noted that the university regulations stipulate that a course can be offered only if a ____ number of students is enrolled.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An orange pencil is not a ____ tool to do your homework with.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government must continue to make every effort to ____ young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the government's decision to invade Iraq.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The suggestion is therefore not reasonable, and the department need not ____ it.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If he was ____ employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although the agreement was compulsory rather than voluntary, it led to ____ military reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a cause of a conflict from a ____ of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police chief gave a very different ____ of the incident than the TV reporter the previous day.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Forests are both an important part of the global ecosystem and an important resource of raw ____ for lumber, paper, and fuelwood.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The airport authorities have decided to ____ passengers to carry only very small amounts of liquid onto the plane.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Problems in school often ____ problems at home.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Check with your academic advisor if you are uncertain whether this will count as a ____ towards your graduation.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is noted that the university regulations ____ that a course can be offered only if a minimum number of students is enrolled.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's a bit surprising at first, how easy it is to measure such a huge ____ as the earth.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that ____ cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The first effort to ____ a revised policy started during the mid-1980s and failed to culminate in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I think we should ____ her work more closely for the next few weeks. She needs to know that we are concerned about her progress.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the importance of the internet.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students choosing this option must ____ a faculty adviser from the departmental faculty who will supervise the student's program.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He said the debate now should exclude events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to ____ the results.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most people are ____ of the problem of global warming, but not many are willing to change the way they live.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science ____ beyond the sports field.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will be required to know the questions and issues that the various authors ____ and the approaches they employ in their research.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a ____ rise in the status of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The supervisor will ____ whether the paper is satisfactory, and thus she or he should make sure the student has enough preparation.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Board may ____ that those actions created a hostile or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an ____ meeting in order to share what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The death of Princess Diana was an ____ that shocked the whole world.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has a heavy accent but this does not ____ with understanding what he means.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Mississippi is a ____ river.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Under the new plan, the garden would remain at its current ____ on Walnut and Virginia streets and the pumping station would be built on the northeast.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This assignment is ____ on September 23.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ is not a sufficient reward for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is a tradition at the school for teachers to ____ a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Journalists were able to ____ the government's secret plan to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "\"Recommended Changes to Student Handbook\" was the next ____ for discussion.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Be sure to isolate and disinfect feeding ____ and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The court decided to ____ the opinion of the mental health specialist.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You should try new technique for learning vocabulary. Your ____ one does not seem very successful.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This looks like a copy. Can you please give me the ____ sheet.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a stereotype of ____ victims.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to ____ the dispute by the efforts of the local community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Asia is our closest region and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and ____ culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has decided to ____ it proposals to increase income tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school made a mistake when buying new computers. They are not ____ with the printers we have.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Click here to review the rules of comma usage when you ____ two independent clauses.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As people are defining a ____ or a problem, sometimes solutions emerge in that moment, in the detail of their description.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ student at our school spends about 90 minutes doing homework every evening.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more ____ than one of greater magnitude that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The information that you receive in today's lesson will ____ you to complete your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the ____ failed to specify in sufficient detail the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to ____ to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous ____ or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I encourage you to spend part of the summer vacation reading. This is an excellent way to ____ your English.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ structure of Iraqi military and civil society collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "African-Americans have disproportionately failed to ____ in American society.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Click here to ____ the rules of comma usage when you combine two independent clauses.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teachers do not always immediately ____ bad behaviour in class. Sometimes it is better to have a quiet talk with the student at the end of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to ____ a photograph when you apply for a job.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The paper was unable to attract sufficient ____ and ceased publication after a few months.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy ____ to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While this was a great idea, the ____ were unclear about the requirements and how it would be graded.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They are quoted at length in Kornbluh's book, The Pinochet File, and ____ cited in the New York Times.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The problems of drug-taking at the school ____ to get out of control.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most important ____ of living near the school is that I can go home for lunch every day.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Twins born from the same egg are called ____ twins. They look exactly the same. Fraternal twins look a little different from each other.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you look at the ____ policies you will notice an item that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Our experience is that small businesses (especially those newly formed) tend to ____ unrealistically low indirect costs.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an ____ operations research study.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student was suffering from mental and physical problems as a result of taking drugs for ____ months.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed assent of the student and signed ____ of the parent.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He may ____ to any political party he pleases, or he may ____ to none.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a ____ issue.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Exam question: Distinguish between the ____ of the iris and the ____ of the cornea.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has changed its ____ to nuclear power now that the cost of oil has been so high for the past few years.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must ____ against the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His research helped establish that identical DNA sequences may behave differently depending on ____ and condition.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Human rights activist John Prendergast, who will present the lecture \"Stopping Genocide\", is ____ the notable speakers coming to campus.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In sports events it is a good idea at the start of the game to ____ energy that you are going to need later.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lack of financial ____ is a significant constraint on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Scientists are working very hard to find a ____ for oil. They hope that one day cars will not pollute the atmosphere.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These programs must ____ factors that may be affecting profits.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They failed to publicly reinforce the message that climate change will having a direct negative impact on ____ security.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are leaving this week for the Dominican Republic to ____ extensive nurse practitioner training.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This gives the teacher and the class the freedom to ____ between learning styles under the same assessment method.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was an ____ idea to allow the students to write their own test.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Media center users must ____ to the same standards of behavior expected of other library visitors.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This also helps you ____ which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most ____ advice that you can give your children is: Be yourself.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The computer is an excellent ____ for language learning.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some farmers, especially those producing corn, hope that biofuels have a bright future, both as a new ____ of cheap energy and as a new ____ of revenue.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Due to the money ____ in schools, teachers are now being charged a high fee for training.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The proponents of disability rights and ____ professionals have come to realize that the concept of accessible ____ has to be rethought.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have made no effort to learn, ____ you will not be entered for the test.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you want too be successful in an English language school or university it is ____ that you learn academic words such as those on this website.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She has continued ____ me with her hard work and positive attitude.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government's ____ in his second term of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company was fined a large ____ of money for attempting to violate pollution regulations.", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "From then on, the government tried to ____ the communists of being enemies of the fatherland.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to be careful not to ____ people that you meet on the internet They may not be who they claim to be..", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some doctors have suggested that their training should be less theoretical and of more ____ use.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have made no effort to learn, ____ you will not be entered for the test.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I think her problems in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further ____ himself from the previous government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to ____ an array of numbers, so that your computer code executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to require food manufacturers to ____ their products as high-, low- or medium fat.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Because of their mobile lifestyle, they did not ____ many objects.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The search results are ____ to include lots of hits that are not particularly relevant to your topic.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your group will need to investigate the ____ characteristics of your city (such as mountains and lakes).", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to ____ himself or herself, the lawyer will not succeed unless he or she can analyze logically.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his ____ to correctly inform the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "China did not ____ nuclear weapons. Having produced several hundred warheads, China stopped building up its military potential.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ between Christianity and the Enlightenment remains a vital issue in the history of Western civilization.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Assad did not want to ____ a cease-fire until Israel evacuated at least those parts of the Golan Heights occupied in the October war.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I have no ____ to students wearing hats in the classroom, but many teachers do.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse global ____ will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students gain professional experience before graduation so that they enter the job market with a ____ advantage.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The document was intended to ____ everything from minerals, through the kingdom of plants, to the highest animals.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Do not commit the serious ____ of believing you can pass the course without doing the coursework.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The good result in the election does not give the government ____ to do whatever it wants.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will need to ____ the images and present them as a narrative or the story of destruction in New Orleans after Katrina.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The need for an alternative ____ to teacher certification has become evident.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The college is aggressively working to ____ engineering education and develop leaders for the 21st century workforce.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While we must oppose all terrorism, and we have many ____ enemies in various parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you try to ____ something that is beyond the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "FLO plays the ____ role as an agent for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "African-Americans have disproportionately failed to ____ in American society.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our ____ surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Bush ____ will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program despite questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Instead of getting involved in the affairs of other countries, the government should concentrate on its ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The text should ____ a concise description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The student was ____ active with the experiment and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The English writing system itself causes no ____ problems to Spanish learners.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While we are less concerned with the politics of Nigeria, we understand that a stable domestic ____ would be to our advantage.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "However, his proposal contains a ____ that is important to recognize and understand.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Wurtz said that these products are not just ____ unnecessary, they are even potentially dangerous.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They further alleged that the removal of the soil would disturb the ____ of the district's drinking water.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The significant differences between the traditional and non-traditional student has prompted the question whether institutions need to ____ their teaching methods to fit the needs of the non-traditional student.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not really her ____ that she comes late to school so often. She lives a long way away, and often gets stuck in a traffic jam.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In his view, the Empire was less a place where England exerted control than where it lost ____ of its own identity.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We will ____ growth and development in our district communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Since it was founded in 1999, the partnership program has been a ____ element in the dramatic increase in applications to the College.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "With winter weather comes the need to prepare your home, automobile and family to ____ with the colder temperatures.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You can't always control what happens to you, but you can always control how you ____ to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you accept a housing assignment in the Summer Allocation and subsequently ____ it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While this was a great idea, the ____ were unclear about the requirements and how it would be graded.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Thus, the results obtained are consistent with the popular ____ that alcohol intoxication causes males to view women as more attractive.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They were unable to ____ the distribution of food supplies because of the deteriorating security situation.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What is the correct key ____ on a calculator for working out a percentage from a fraction?", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Studies have shown that students ____ jobs that they like to jobs that pay well.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The science teacher planned to ____ how water evaporates more quickly in hot temperatures.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This past summer, after a vacation to Japan, I realized that what I had been eating in America was not ____ Japanese food.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The western end of the ____ route appears to have developed earlier than the eastern end, principally because of the development of the empires in the west.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you work harder, you will ____ a better grade next term.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When reporting scores, both the student's ____ and the number of students in the class must be stated.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental ____ are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ study conducted by Dr. Francisco Moreno at the University of Arizona tested the effects of psilocybin psychotherapy on patients with obsessive disorders.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We do not yet know the implication for the government of the ____ rise in house prices.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was not evident to many people why the government had decided to ____ smoking in all restaurants but to allow it in its own buildings.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The loose and often unclear ____ of the organizational responsibilities enabled energetic managers to network.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is never too late to ____ healthy habits! American Institute for Cancer Research.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There will be a ____ class after school today for those who want extra practice for the test.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We used this information to construct a continuous measure of the ____ of subject-specific coursework to total coursework.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not ____ in any other activities immediately prior to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The explanation for this extraordinary decision lies in the immediate ____ surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We further believe that the general quality of student writing will not improve unless we as a department are ____ to state explicitly the standards we require.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to ____ a paper on how his research team broke the code of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences ____ improve performance over time.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her problems began to ____ themselves after she was absent for more than a month.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ example of ambiguity is the sentence: \"I do not like visiting aunts.\"", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is no ____ student. She can speak 5 languages and play the piano to a very high standard.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This was a ____ attempt at addressing the issue, and not a very scholarly or intellectual attempt.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Gladwin County decided to suspend the sale of dogs from its animal shelter in ____ to give citizens the chance to review the county's earlier decision.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If children of seven years and older will be included in the study, an ____ agreement is necessary.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has a heavy accent but this does not ____ with understanding what he means.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to intervene in the dispute over the ____ minister.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some parents do not ____ how difficult it is to provide an education that will meet the needs of all students.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will culminate in a ____ of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We faced an ____ problem over 10 years ago and couldn't solve it then, either.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The boss decided not to ____ her employee's request to leave work early.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is only one ____ in your writing. You put: He play tennis instead of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ the plan after a meeting with the parents.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "One ____ of the problem that we have not yet considered is: How are we going to pay for it?", "Opt_1": "element", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She was able to ____ the Smartboard screen controls so that the presentation was visible to everyone.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Although we did ____ the faculty in the revised teaching methods, in hindsight our ____ing was not thorough enough to prepare them for the new course.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What the headlines failed to ____ was that democratic parties captured more than 60 percent of the ballots cast.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will ____ much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In Germany most students have the chance to gain ____ experience in an office or factory, before deciding what job they would like to do.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company was fined a large sum of money for attempting to ____ pollution regulations.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You have not got these words in the right order. In German the main verb must be the second ____ in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "During this course you will review your knowledge of German, by focusing on the four language skills, ____ speaking, listening, reading and writing.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Check your ____ to be sure that class times do not overlap.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "way"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For this task, instructors present a series of steps in a mixed ____ and students are asked to re-____ the items into the correct sequence.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war ____ Iraq is an appropriate occasion to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to overcome its ____ to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was a particular reason for this: psychologically, it fitted her deeply personal sense of the appropriate ____ between the sexes.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government took the ____ decision to decrease tax.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The union leaders promised to ____ for a longer lunch break for the employees.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We designed an experiment to ____ blood from embryonic rats.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The beauty of the telephone, and something that the telegraph lacked, was that it required no ____ to operate.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The more powerful computers will continue to ____ all aspects of life.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The name of this website is 'A ____ to learning English.'", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I think that everyone going for the maximum marks, the highest grades and the greatest possible output is not the best ____ for a well-rounded individual.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They found that specific, simple steps can ____ reduce the number of drivers who drink.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I don't know how I always ____ to get such a good grade. I never work particularly hard.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school offers basketball ____ in the vacation.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was agriculture that allowed civilizations to ____ growth.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The situation in Iraq continues to ____ the government's attention.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The companies did not release the ____ results of the trial until almost two years after the trial was finished.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a ____ search strategy has paid off.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She has learned from her mother's experience, however, and does not ____ the error her mother made.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She receives so many requests similar to yours that she finds it impossible to ____ with all of them, much as she would like to do so.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is essential to consider her difficulties at school in the ____ of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum ____ for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Despite the overall satisfaction that the program was ____ successful, there are several ways in which the program could have been improved.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "So, what's the point of all this hindsight and what do we stand to ____ from it?", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My overall ____ of him since he joined the class is very positive.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If faculty suspect that a mental health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should ____ the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Candidates must ____ a high level of responsibility, the ability to work independently, and a strong commitment to customer service.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her ability and experience to this new problem.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will see the ____ of the problem on the left and the solution on the right.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His ____ is that if we don't cut taxes, then unemployment will rise.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But he did not confine himself to theoretical matters alone. He now drew attention to the ____ of American minority students on campus.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable ____ to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is ____ to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies demonstrate that the ____ was not able to eliminate discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The fact that speech is likely to result in some violence or in destruction of property is not enough to ____ its suppression.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government cannot afford to be ____ about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Computer viruses ____ themselves to documents such as word processing files and spreadsheets.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We do not yet know the implication for the government of the rapid ____ in house prices.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be ____ and to highlight all that is important.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some beach systems showed significant loss of sand in the ____ from 1964.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We have ____ that students are more likely to complete a community health project if they join a team.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Could you use informal writing tasks to ____ thinking and learning?", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We do not yet know the implication for the government of the rapid ____ in house prices.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There was a loud argument in the cafeteria today. I had to ____ before it turned into a fight.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't appreciate a ____ from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was given to the grandmother by her grandfather in 1852, when the latter was a ____ of the California assembly.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to ____ this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The unemployment figures ____ that the recent changes in tax have been successful.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for the bad test scores is that the teacher was new and inexperienced.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Because of the interactive nature of the classroom, absences will significantly ____ your performance in the course.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We ____ all our efforts and resources to the education and preparation of all students.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new team coach is an ____ of the view: No pain, no gain!", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are not yet ready to go to the next ____ of ESL.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Using computer modeling, he was able to ____ the relationship between the strength of a stellar wind and the age of a star.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government announced that it was pleased with the steady fall in unemployment during its ____ in office.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My biggest ____ about the book is that Gruchy did not insert his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is no ____ student. She can speak 5 languages and play the piano to a very high standard.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "But when planned and deliberate policy forces the price of oil down without good ____ reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Despite the ____ amount of effort invested in her language teaching she was not able to construct grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The correct ____ of this text requires recovering certain implicit information that relies on commonsense knowledge.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We need to ____ a test to measure the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the former grade will ____ on the record with an appropriate notation.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It offers an ____ solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "ESL students fare better in classrooms where the teacher is ____ of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in ____ but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Drug abusers also show prefrontal cortex ____ities; it is possible that ____ behaviour may be linked to drug use.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not obey a police ____ to halt and was shot.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Force is not always the best ____ to get people to change their behaviour, and especially not their way of thinking.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Yet there were conflicts there too, and the immigrants did not ____ easily and completely into Israeli culture.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are recommended to record every significant ____ about each of your customers.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In August, UMBC will ____ a new home page on our Web site.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's ____ for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The final examination shall be designed to ____ a period not to exceed two hours.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The headmaster called a meeting to try to ____ the dispute between the two teachers.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}]]